Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art financial records, 1872-1988 COR0004.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Deeds and legal documents, 1861-1969; Series 2
  Contains cancelled loan notes; Congressional bills & acts regarding the Corcoran Gallery's incorporation; correspondence, some in French & Italian; deeds, land titles, Trustee resolutions, and wills. Materials of interest include W.W. Corcoran's deed of the Gallery to the Board of Trustees and related materials; W.W. Corcoran' s will; Corcoran rent claim against the U.S. Government for use of the Gallery during the Civil War; the purchase of land (Square 171) for the new Gallery site, property of the "Sisters of the Visitation" in Georgetown, and the deed to the Washington Gallery of Modern Art.
  Separated Materials note
  Art loan forms from 1873-82 were removed from these files and placed with the Registrar's Records in Record Group 5.
- Trustee finance records, 1894-1979; Series 3
  The series is arranged chronologically.
  Related Archival Materials note
  Researchers should also investigate the Trustee Committee meeting minutes and reports (RG 1) for a complete account of Trustee finance materials in the Archives.
  Contains correspondence, meeting minutes, memoranda, and (bulk) Treasurer's reports -- annual, semi-annual, and quarterly. The records of Treasurers Charles C. Glover (1894-1921), Robert Fleming (1928-48 ), Treasurer Corcoran Thom, Jr. (1948- 68), and Finance & Investment Committee member Frederick Bradley make up the bulk of the series. Materials document the overall financial condition of the Gallery/School on a quarterly, semi-annual, and annual basis. Included in the series is one letterpress copybook of Treasurer Glover from 1894-1921. Subjects of special note' include the Corcoran's financial arrangement with George Washington University regarding studio classes, C.P. Minnigerode's retirement, the Oyster Bequest, and the formation of the Consolidated Endowment Fund in 1967. People who appear prominently in the records include Frederick Bradley, Robert Fleming, Charles C. Glover, Frank Parulski, I.J. Roberts, Corcoran Thom Jr., and Robert L. Walsh.
  - Treasurer's letterpress copy book, Charles Glover, 1894-1921; Series 3 (Box 23, Ledger 1)
  - Minutes of the Finance and Investment Committee, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Treasurer's Semi-Annual Report, 1916 May - December; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Treasurer: Misc. Correspondence, 1930; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1936; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Treasurer's Semi-Annual Report: 6-12, 1938; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Treasurer's Semi-Annual Report:1-12, 1939; Series 3 (Box 3, Folders 41-42)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Correspondence and Memos, 1939; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Semi-Annual Report: 1-12, 1940; Series 3 (Box 3, Folders 44-45)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1940; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Semi-Annual Report: 1-12, 1941; Series 3 (Box 3, Folders 47-48)
  - Treasurer's Material Re. George Washington Univ. Affiliation, 1941; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres and Memos: 1 - 12, 1941; Series 3 (Box 3, Folders 50-51)
  - Finance and Investment Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1942; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Finance and Investment Committee: Committee Reports, 1942; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Semi-Annual Report: 1-12, 1942; Series 3 (Box 3, Folders 54-55)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres.: Memos, 1942; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Semi-Annual Report: 1-12, 1943; Series 3 (Box 3, Folders 57-58)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1943; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Semi-Annual Report: 1-12, 1944; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 1-2)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1944; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Semi-Annual Report: 1-12, 1945; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 4-5)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1945; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Semi-Annual Report: 1-12, 1946; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 7-8)
  - Treasurer's Correspondence: Minnigerode Retirement and Pension, 1946; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Correspondence - Oyster Bequest, 1946; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1946; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1947; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 12-15)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1947; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1948; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 17-21)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1948; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1949; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 23-26)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1949; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1950; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 28-31)
  - Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1951; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 32-34)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1951; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Treasurer's Misc. Corres. and Memos, 1951; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Finance and Investment Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1952; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1952; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 38-40)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1952; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly Report, 1953; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 42-44)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1953; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1954; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1954; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 47-50)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1954; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 51-52)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1955; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1955; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 54-56)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1955; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Misc. Corres., 1956; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1956; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 59-61)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1956; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1957; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1957; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 64-66)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1957; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 67-68)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1958; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1958; Series 3 (Box 4, Folders 70-73)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1958; Series 3 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report (Final), 1958; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1959; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1959; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 3-5)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1959; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1960; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1960; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 8-10)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1960; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Financial and Investment Committee - Misc. Corres., 1961; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1961; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 13-15)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1961; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1962; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1962; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 18-20)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1962; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Misc. Corres., 1963; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly Report, 1963; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 23-24)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1963; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Misc. Corres., 1964; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1964; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 27-29)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1964; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Misc. Corres., 1965; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1965; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 32-34)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1965; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1966; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 36-38)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1966; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Consolidated Endoument Fund - Establishment, 1967; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Consolidated Endoument Fund - Valuation, 1967 September; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1967; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1967; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 43 - 45)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1967; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Consolidated Endowment Fund - Reports and Valuation, 1968; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1968; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly Report, 1968; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 49-50)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1968; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Consolidated Endoument Fund - Reports, 1969; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Consolidated Endoument Fund - Valuation, 1969; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1969; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly and Semi-Annual Report, 1969; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 55-56)
  - Treasurer's Annual Report, 1969; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Consolidated Endoument Fund - Valuation, 1970; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1970; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Treasurer's Quarterly Report, 1970; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1970; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Consolidated Endoument Fund - Valuation, 1971; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Finance and Investment Comm. - Misc. Corres., 1971; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1971 April; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Louise Home Tax Exemption, 1972; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Misc. Correspondence, 1972; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 66-67)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Misc. Correspondence, 1973 - 1974; Series 3 (Box 5, Folders 68-69)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Finances - School Payment to Gallery Analysis, 1976; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Meeting Minutes, Memos, 1978; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Meeting, 1978 July 17; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Meetings, Memos, 1978; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Audit Committee - Draft of Audit Report, 1979; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Finance and Investment Committee - Meetings and Memos, Undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Gallery and school budgets, 1934-1981; Series 4
  Materials are arranged chronologically.
  Contains materials on the Gallery and School annual budgets including budget working papers, proposed budgets, and revised & final budgets for each year. The series also includes a wide variety of accompanying budgetary materials which have become increasingly elaborate for more recent years. These include financial & estimated income statements, operation of the budget statements (quarterly), operating income statements (quarterly), combined statements of receipts (quarterly), condition of the funds statements (annual), statements of income & expense (monthly), end-of-the-year budget estimates, budget adjustments, cash flow statements, and some departmental budgets and quarterly & annual stock statements. It should be noted that until the late 1960s, the Treasurer/Assistant Treasurer prepared the Gallery and School budgets. From the late 1960s on, the Comptroller/Budget Director has handled budget preparation. Persons who appear frequently include Robert Fleming, Gwendolyn Goffe, Frank Parulski, I.J. Roberts, Robert Steigler, and Corcoran Thorn Jr. Researchers should check the financial ledgers in Series I for pertinent information.
  - Revised Budget, 1934; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Proposed Budget, 1935; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Proposed Budget, 1936; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Proposed Budget, 1937; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Proposed Budget, 1938; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Proposed Budget, 1939; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Proposed Budget, 1940; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Real Estate Notes, 1940; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Proposed Budget, 1941; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Budget: Financial Statements, Estimated Income, 1941; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Budget: Operation of Budget, 1941; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Proposed Budget, 1941; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Revised Budget, 1942; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Budget: Financial Statements, Estimated Income, 1942; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Operation of the Budget - Quarterly, 1942; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Budget: Miscellaneous, 1942; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Proposed Budget, 1943; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Revised Budget, 1943; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Operation of the Budget - Quarterly, 1943; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Proposed Budget, 1944; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Financial Statements, Estimated Income, 1944; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Operation of Budget - Quarterly, 1944; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Proposed Budget, 1945; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Financial Statements, Estimated Income, 1945; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Operation of the Budget - Quarterly, 1945; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Proposed Budget, 1946; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Financial Statements, 1946; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Operation of the Budget - Quarterly, 1946; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Proposed Budget, 1947; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Financial Statements, Estimated Income, 1947; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Operation of the Budget, 1947; Series 4 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Art School Budget, 1947; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Budget, 1948; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Balances of the Funds, Estimated Income, 1948; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Operation of Budget, 1948; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Budget-Miscellaneous, 1948; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gallery: Proposed Budget, 1949; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Gallery Budget, 1949; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1949; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gallery: Budget-Miscellaneous, 1949; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Art School Budget, 1948-1949; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gallery Budget, 1949; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gallery Budget: Operation of Budget-Quarterly, 1950; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1950; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Art School Budget, 1949-1950; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Gallery Budget, 1951; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1951; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Gallery: Statement of Operational Income-Quarterly, 1951; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1951; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Art School Budget, 1950-1951; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Gallery Budget, 1952; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1952; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Gallery: Statement of Operational Income-Quarterly, 1952; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1952; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Art School Budget, 1951-1952; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Gallery: Budget, 1953; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1953; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Gallery: Statement of Operational Income-Quarterly, 1953; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1953; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Art School Budget, 1952-1953; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Gallery Budget, 1954; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1954; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Gallery: Statement of Operational Income-Quarterly, 1954; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1954; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Art School Budget, 1953-1954; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Gallery Budget: Working Papers, 1955; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Gallery Budget, 1955; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1955; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1955; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Art School Budget, 1954-55; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Gallery Budget: Working Papers, 1956; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Gallery Budget, 1956; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1956; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1956; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1956; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Art School Budget, 1955-1956; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Gallery Budget, 1957; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-6, 1957; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1957; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1957; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1957; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Art School Budget, 1957; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Gallery Budget, 1958; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Gallery Revised Budget, 1958; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-6, 1958; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1958; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1958; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1958; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Art School Budget, 1957-1958; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Gallery Budget, 1959; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1959; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1959; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1959; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Art School Budget, 1958-1959; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Gallery Budget, 1960; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1960; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1960; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1960; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Art School Budget, 1959-1960; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Gallery Budget: Working Papers, 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Gallery Budget, 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-6, 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Art School Budget, 1960-1961; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Gallery Budget, 1962; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-6, 1962; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1962; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Gallery: Combined Statements-Receipts(Quarterly), 1962; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1962; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Art School Budget, 1961-1962; Series 4 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Gallery Budget, 1963; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Gallery Budget-Revised, 1963; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1963; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Gallery: Operation of Budget 1-3, 1963; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Gallery: Operation of Budget 1-9, 1963; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-12, 1963; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Art School Budget, 1962-1963; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Gallery Budget, 1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-6, 1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-3, 1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-9, 1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-12, 1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Art School Budget, 1963-1964; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gallery Budget, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-3, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-9, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-12, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Art School Budget, 1964-1965; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Gallery Budget, 1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-3, 1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-9, 1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-12, 1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Art School Budget, 1965-1966; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Gallery Budget, 1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-6, 1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-3, 1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-9, 1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-12, 1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Art School: Proposed Budget, 1966-1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Art School: Budget, 1966-1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Art School Budget-Miscellaneous, 1966-1967; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Gallery Budget, 1968; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1968; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-3, 1968; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-9, 1968; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget 1-12, 1968; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1968; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Art School Budget, 1967-1968; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Gallery Budget, 1969; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1969; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Gallery: Dupont Center Budget, 1968-1969; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Art School Budget, 1968-1969; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Gallery Budget, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Gallery: Clark Fund, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds 1-12, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Gallery: Departmental Budgets, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 54)